ketosummit.com 2016-12-29

# Privacy Policy - The Keto Summit

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, or take a similar action.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To process transactions (Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.)
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
  * To send periodic emails (The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.)

**Ad Targeting Policy**

This Ad Targeting Policy describes how we use and share data for online targeted marketing purposes.

We may share information about you and other customers collectively (but not specifically identifiable to you) with our parent company, our affiliated companies, and with third parties. This information includes:

  * Demographic information (gender, estimated age, and general geographic location, and your estimated purchase ability);
  * Summarized census information and other publicly available information (estimated education level, homeownership status, and estimated occupation type); and
  * Your inferred and expressed interests, including transactional information and product interests we derive from your visits to some of the sites listed above.

The recipients of this information use it to develop and deliver targeted advertising on our websites and on the websites of third parties. The information is used only for marketing purposes. It is not used to make targeted offers that are priced differently based on estimated purchase ability.

The targeted advertising resulting from this information sharing is related to common product and service categories, such as magazines, subscriptions, weight-loss programs, supplements, books, events, online summits, and similar categories that you see advertised routinely. These advertisements are not based on data relating to adult content, individual or aggregate health information or records, or information relating to your financial accounts.

We use cookies to facilitate the sharing of this information while you are online. Information in these cookies is updated from time to time to ensure that it is up to date and relevant. In order to appropriately safeguard the information in them, as described above, these cookies are encrypted. At this time we do not respond to “do not track” browser signals.

We may display various types of advertisements on the sites you visit (including sites such as Facebook and Google) for a variety of reasons. In the same way that we use information about you to customize or personalize the content or services we provide, we may also use information to make the ads you see more relevant for you, and more effective for advertisers. We may also use information from other companies or sites to assist in determining the effectiveness of advertising.

In some cases, the ads shown to you are based on your activity on our sites or on other sites or information appended from offline sources. This is often called targeted advertising, behavioral targeting, interest-based advertising, or customized ads. When you visit one of our sites, you may receive a “cookie” or other technology that helps us note, in an anonymized way, that you visited that site. This information is then used to help us display ads that are more relevant, both on our sites and on other sites (including the Google Ad Network, Facebook, Twitter, and other ad networks and social platforms). Note that the information shared with advertising networks is always with a unique identifier, and does not include personally identifiable information such as your name, email address, etc.

**Consumer Control**

While it is not possible to turn off all advertising, you can use your browser to control your experience. When you clear the cookies in your browser, you may clear the information used to build a behavioral profile. Depending on the browser you are using, you can also choose to block third party cookies (such as cookies from ad networks) or browse in a private browsing mode. As new technologies emerge to control your experience, we may provide additional information or instructions to manage your preferences.

Many opt outs are based on a cookie set by your browser that prevents the collection of data connected to a unique anonymous ID. If you opt-out using this method, the opt-out will generally last for 1-5 years. Please note that clearing the cookies in your browser may cancel the opt-out. In conjunction with the Digital Advertising Alliance, we offer the Cookie Protector, which will ensure that your opt-out settings persist regardless of clearing your cookies.

**How Do We Protect Your Information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be kept on file for more than 60 days.

**Do We Use Cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information). We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

**Do We Disclose Any Information to Outside Parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. This also does not include any third party to whom we may sell or transfer our business. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third Party Links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we will not request any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://ketosummit.com/terms-and-conditions

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

P.O. Box 732  
Morgan Hill, CA 95038  
USA  
support@ketosummit.com
